botach.com 2015-10-01

# Policies

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for ([https://www.botach.com](https://www.botach.com/)). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 

1.     What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 

2.     What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 

3.     The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 

4.     How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

** Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**   
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

** Your Access to and Control Over Information**   
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: 

  * See what data we have about you, if any. 
  * Change/correct any data we have about you. 
  * Have us delete any data we have about you. 
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

** Security**   
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

** If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 888 344-5145 or  via email (cs@botach.com).**

**Return Policy**

Our return policy is backed by a 100% money back guarantee. You have 15 days from the time of your orders delivery to notify us of any intent to return merchandise. You can fill out an RMA# Form (Return Authorization) on our Customer Service page. **All products must be returned in original condition and contain all manufacturer packaging and tags.**

If an item proves to be defective within the 15-day return policy or is shipped incorrectly, we will be more than happy to cover the return shipping to have the item replaced or credited to you. We may ask that you return merchandise directly to the manufacturer if it is after our 15-day return policy if the product is covered by any manufacturer warranty.

**Shipping Policy**

All of our orders are shipped UPS or USPS . With our Free Standard Ground Shipping option we retain the right to choose the best method for freight. If the ultimate destination for your package requires a specific method because the area has limited access, you are required to pay for shipping. A customer is also required to pay for shipping if he/she needs expedited shipping .

**Cancellation Policy**

You may cancel your order via email at cs@botach.com or by phone at 1-888-344-5145 if a tracking number is not yet available for the item or order. The sooner you do it, the better it is as we cannot guarantee return of package once it’s in transit and you will be required to cover any fuel charges if the package has already shipped and you decided to cancel late.

Funds take anywhere from 24-72 hours to be processed back into your account. You are always notified of any credit issued to you via email.

**International Policy**

Yes, we do ship outside of the U.S. However, the methods of payment for international orders are different than those nationwide. We do adhere to all ITAR rules and regulations for the exportation of restricted items.

**Please note:** Botach reserves the right to correct critical errors on our website, as we are constantly updating it.
